The International Labor Organization says the number of people without jobs is
increasing. In its latest update on global employment trends,
International Labor Organization says the number of people without jobs is
the International Labor Organization says the number of people without jobs is
increasing. In its latest update on global employment trends,
Agency says projections of the number of people this year range from 210 million to
nearly 240 million people.
The Agency says projections of the number of people this year range from 210 million
to nearly 240 million people.
The Agency says projections of the number of unemployed people this year range from
210 million to nearly 240 million people.
The report warns that 200 million poor workers are at risk of joining the ranks of
people living on less than $2 per day in the past three years.
The Director General of the International Labor Organization, Juan Somavia,
notes that some countries have taken measures to address the effects of the global
crisis. The Director General of the International Labor Organization,
Juan Somavia, notes that some countries have taken measures to address the effects
of the global crisis.
However, he points out that many countries have not done so, and based on past
experiences, takes four to five years after economic recovery.
However, he